
<time hour="13" min="07"/> One of the stranger explanations for the looting
<time hour="12" min="47"/> Case relating to theft of £1,133 of clothes from Hugo Boss on Sloane Square on Monday about to be heard at Westminster Magistrates Court, James Hall reports.
<time hour="09" min="00"/> David Cameron has just begun a fourth day of COBRA meetings. The Prime Minister will be sitting across the table from senior police chiefs who are reportedly furious with the criticism he and Theresa May made of their early handling of the riots.
<time hour="6" min="30" meridiem="am" timezone="EST"/>: Welcome to our live coverage of Hurricane Irene as it tracks up the eastern coast of the United States and heads for New York.
<time hour="12" min="54" meridiem="pm" timezone="EST"/>: One of the most significant lines to come out of New York mayor Michael Bloomberg's news conference earlier (see <time hour="9" min="36" meridiem="am" timezone="EST"/>) was his suggestion that power would be cut pre-emptively to Lower Manhattan (from where I am blogging). Fortunately, Consolidated Edison, the power company, has said it has no such plans.
{S}The biggest outages so far are in North Carolina, where more than 500,000 households were without power by afternoon. South-eastern Virginia is also experiencing blackouts. The power company Dominion Resources said about a third of its 212,000 customers in south-eastern Virginia were without power by <time hour="4" meridiem="pm"/>.
{S}Live Play-by-play broadcast of Varsity games
{S}Game coverage begins <time hour="7" min="00" meridiem="pm"/> with kick off <time hour="7" min="30" meridiem="pm"/> on Friday nights
{S}680 WRGC Sports Coverage Includes: Pre-game Show, Half-time Report and a Post-game show.
{S}Live weeknights <time hour="5" min="30"/> and <time hour="10" min="00"/>
{S}Pahang police chief said the men, aged 17 and 55 years, were in a car and heading towards the national capital when they were apprehended <time hour="11" min="45" meridiem="pm"/>.
{S}Police found a machete and two knives inside the car, he told Bernama, adding that there were no illegal rallies reported in Pahang so far.
{S}In MELAKA, police arrested three men at a road block at Simpang Ampat, Alor Gajah, <time hour="1" meridiem="am"/> today for possessing Bersih t-shirts.
{S}Melaka police chief Datuk Chuah Ghee Lye said they were on their way from Pontian, Johor to Kuala Lumpur.
{S}"As <time hour="11" meridiem="am"/> today, there were no reports of illegal rallies in Melaka. We are monitoring the situation," he told Bernama.